Arabia
Marist College
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
- Arabia, Lowell Thomas Papers; Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601; Lowell Thomas; 1.2.3
  - Graphics Materials, 2
    - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
      - Lantern slides, 2.1.2
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Photographs, 2.1
              - Arabian “Hindu” bathing on deck of S.S. Ozarda, 1918; 1262.1 (Box 1262)
                4x5
              - Sheep on board deck of S.S. Ozarda [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Our fellow passengers crossing the Red Sea], 1918; 1262.2
                film
              - Wadi Araba, caravan in distance, 1918; 1262.3
              - Emir Feisal [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Emir Feisal, now King of Mesopotamia (Irak)], 1918; 1263.1 (Box 1263)
                5x7
              - His Royal Highness Emir Feisal, 1918; 1263.2
              - T. E. Lawrence and Emir Feisal at right conferring with Bedouin sheiks [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Feisal and Lawrence conferring with Bedouin Sheiks], 1918; 1263.3
              - Holy Mosque, summit of Mount Hor, Lowell Thomas in foreground, Petra, 1918; 1265.1 (Box 1265)
              - Tomb discovered by accident, Petra, 1918; 1265.2